Guide to the New York University Archives Audiovisual Collection AV
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Audiovisual Collection
1948-2011
New York University Archives
AV
5034 items
380.6 Megabytes in 2 computer files
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access CDs for audiovisual materials in the collection are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact University Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - In the Year 2000: Cleveland Amory, circa 1967; AV1; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 1)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:52)
  - In the Year 2000: Beers, Mr. & Sinder, Leon, May 14, 1968; AV2 (Box 1, Reel AV2, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV2)
    Scope and Contents
    Housing Annotations: "1. National Dairy Taped May 14, 1968 'Food' Mr. Beers; 2. Leon Sinder, Prof. of Sociology Long Island University Not for Air The City and Sociological Life by 2000"
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 33 min.
  - In the Year 2000: Dr. DeCarlo -- IBM, circa 1967; AV4; 1 sound tape reels (Box 1, Reel 4, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 2)
    Access copy
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 13:2
  - In the Year 2000: Dr. Ettinger -- Cryonics, circa 1967; AV7; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 7)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:49)
  - In the Year 2000: Maurice Girodias, circa 1967; AV8; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 8)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:50)
  - In the Year 2000: Gold, Thomas -- Astronomy, circa 1967; AV9 (Box 1, Reel AV9, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV9)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 16 min.
  - In the Year 2000: Goodau, circa 1967; AV10 (Box 1, Reel AV10, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV10)
  - In the Year 2000: Dr. Gordon Gould -- HoloBeam, Inc., circa 1967; AV11; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 11)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:40)
  - In the Year 2000: Dr. John Jacobs -- Ultrasound Image Devices -- Northwestern University, circa 1967; AV12; 1 sound tape reels
    General
    Original tape box labeled with note "Tail up"
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 12)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:54)
  - In the Year 2000: Bruce Ladd -- Author of "Crisis in Credibility", circa 1967; AV13
    Physical Description
    Original tape box labeled with note "(5? min)"
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 13)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:55)
  - In the Year 2000: Mulgrue, George, circa 1967; AV14 (Box 1, Reel AV14, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV14)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 15 min.
  - In the Year 2000: Pike, Bishop James, circa 1967; AV16 (Box 1, Reel AV16, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV16)
    Housing Annotations: "P. Heller"
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 17 min.
  - In the Year 2000: Irwin, Ross, circa 1967; AV20 (Box 1, Reel AV20, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV20)
  - In the Year 2000: Shonting, Howard -- Real Estate Buying, circa 1967; AV25 (Box 1, Reel AV25, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV25)
    Housing Annotations: "The Real Estate boards on NY Executive Up, Reel 1"
  - In the Year 2000: Rustum Roy, circa 1967; AV21
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 21)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:53)
  - In the Year 2000: R.J. Rutherford -- American Gas Association, circa 1967; AV22
    Original tape box labeled with note: "The first eleven or twelve minutes can be eliminated. Predictions do not begin until after that period."
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 22)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:27)
  - In the Year 2000: Dr. Glenn T. Seaborg -- Chairman, U.S. Atomic Energy Commission, January 16, 1968; AV23
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 23)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:26)
  - In the Year 2000: Dr. Von Braun -- "By the Year 2000", March 15, 1968; AV27; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box includes following notes: "copy 3 3/2 ips," "Letter [?] to Falk 5/29/68"
    - Original Recording (Box 1, Reel 27)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:23)
  - In the Year 2000: U.S. Department of Agriculture, March 28, 1968; AV29 (Box 1, Reel AV29, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV29)
    Housing Annotations: "231-E; See statement NYU; 7 1/2 ips; time 4:33"
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 6 min.
  - Brown, Lester -- Science, undated; AV31 (Box 1, Reel AV31, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV31)
    Housing Annotations: "Lester Brown, Administrator, Internat'l Agrig. Develop. Service.; Lester R. Brown Administrator, International Agricultural Development Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, Washington D.C. 20250; Content not good for radio. Okay for book. Please make a copy of this and send it to Mr. Brown at the above address. His public info office wants a copy of the raw tape as soon as possible."
  - Guttmacher, Dr. Alan -- Population and Birth Control, February 8, 1968; AV32 (Box 1, Reel AV32, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV32)
    Housing Annotations: Original box reads, "P. Heller."
  - In the Year 2000: Hornig, Donald (tape 1 of 2), circa 1967; AV33 (Box 1, Reel AV33, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV33)
    Housing Annotations: "Donald Hornig, Science Advisor to the President Reel #1, Make Work Copy"
  - In the Year 2000: Hornig, Donald (tape 2 of 2), circa 1967; AV34 (Box 1, Reel AV34, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV34)
    Housing Annotations: "Donald Hornig, Science Advisor to President, Reel #2, Do not make work copy"
  - Jacobson, Dr. Cecil -- Science, undated; AV35 (Box 1, Reel AV35, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV35)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 14 min.
  - Mayer, Dr. Jean -- Science, undated; AV36 (Box 1, Reel AV36, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV36)
    Housing Annotations: "Dr. Jean Mayer, Department of Nutrition Harvard University Medical School. Taped May 3 at 2:30PM." No year specified.
  - Mesthene, Dr. Emmanuel & Howells, William, undated; AV37 (Box 1, Reel AV37, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV37)
    Housing Annotations: "Dr. Emmanuel Mesthene, Director Harvard Program Science + Technology Taped May 3 - 10:00am; William Howells, Prof of Anthropology - his last comment on tape, referring to genes is in reference to his first statements. Taped May 3 - 11:00am" (Year not specified)
  - Rusk, Dr. -- NYU Medical Center, December 13, 1967; AV38 (Box 1, Reel AV38, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV38)
  - Salisbury, Harrison & Ellis, Dr. Albert, undated; AV39 (Box 1, Reel AV39, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV39)
    Housing Annotations: "Harrison Salisbury #2 Newspapers; Dr. Albert Ellis, sex"
  - Skehan, S.J., Father -- Boston College Geology Department, May 3, 1968; AV40 (Box 1, Reel AV40, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV40)
    Housing Annotations: "Father Skehan, S.J. Boston College - Geology Dept. Taped May 3, 1968 at 4PM; Great Show!!!"
  - Spar, Dr. Jerome -- Weather, undated; AV41 (Box 1, Reel AV41, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV41)
    Housing Annotations: "Dr. Jerome Spar, 12/13, WEATHER" (year not specified)
  - Udenfriend, Dr. Sidney -- Science, undated; AV42 (Box 1, Reel AV42, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV42)
    Housing Annotations: "Dr. Sidney Udenfriend, National Institute of Health Clinical Biochemistry"
  - Adler, Mortimer, undated; AV43 (Box 1, Reel AV43, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV43)
    Housing Annotations: "Mortimer Adler 11/16 'The Difference of Man, and the Difference it Makes' 8:30 ORIGINAL" (year not specified)
  - Boyd, Alan S., undated; AV44 (Box 1, Reel AV44, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV44)
    Housing Annotations: "Alan Boyd, Secretary of the Department of Transportation." Box includes taped newspaper image of Boyd.
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 7 min.
  - Transportation, Department of, undated; AV45 (Box 1, Reel AV45, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV45)
    Housing Annotations: "Transportation 4:45 (MASTER)"
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 10 min.
  - Boyd, Malcolm, undated; AV46 (Box 1, Reel AV46, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV46)
    Housing Annotations: "bad master"
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 23 min.
  - Clutte, Mr., April 1, 1968; AV47 (Box 1, Reel AV47, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV47)
    Housing Annotations: "Mr. Clutte, First National City Bank, taped 4/1/68 at 11:15AM"
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 20 min.
  - Cooper, Gordon -- Astronaut, November 27, 1967; AV48 (Box 1, Reel AV48, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV48)
    Housing annotations: "11/27/67 Astronaut Gordon Cooper; Cooper runs 9:45. Heller." Included with box are two sheets of biographical facts about Cooper from NASA.
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 13 min.
  - Corrigan, Dean, undated; AV49 (Box 1, Reel AV49, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV49)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 11 min.
  - Eisenbud, undated; AV50 (Box 1, Reel AV50, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV50)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 12 min.
  - Fogelson, Mr. & Fidler, Gail, March 24, 1968; April 1, 1968; AV51 (Box 1, Reel AV51, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV51)
    Housing annotations: "Mr. Fogelson - Sachs Quality Stores, taped March 24, 1968; Gail Fidler - NYU State Psychiatric Institute, Psych. Occupational Therapy - taped 4/1/68 at 1PM"
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 32 min.
  - Gabor, undated; AV52 (Box 1, Reel AV52, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV52)
    Housing Annotations: "Gabor Master." No other identifying information.
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 5 min.
  - Goodson, Mark, undated; AV53 (Box 1, Reel AV53, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV53)
  - Greenwalt, undated; AV54 (Box 1, Reel AV54, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV54)
    Housing Annotations: Alternate spelling "Greenwald." No other identifying information.
  - Heckscher -- Parks Commissioner, undated; AV55 (Box 1, Reel AV55, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV55)
    Likely referring to August Heckscher, former New York City Parks Commissioner from 1967-1972.
  - Joffe, undated; AV56 (Box 1, Reel AV56, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV56)
  - Jones, Chris, February 14, 1968; AV57 (Box 1, Reel AV57, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV57)
  - Logan, Daniel, undated; AV58 (Box 1, Reel AV58, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV58)
  - Mannes, Marya, undated; AV59 (Box 1, Reel AV59, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV59)
  - Mead, Dr. Margaret, undated; AV60 (Box 1, Reel AV60, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV60)
  - Mead, Dr. Margaret & Hilsman, Roger, undated; AV61 (Box 1, Reel AV61, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV61)
    Housing Annotations: "Dr. M. Mead; Roger Hilsman Asst. Sect. of State for Eastern Affairs"
  - Patai, undated; AV62 (Box 1, Reel AV62, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV62)
  - Peale, Dr. Norman Vincent, undated; AV63 (Box 1, Reel AV63, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV63)
  - Rembar, Charles, undated; AV64 (Box 1, Reel AV64, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV64)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 18 min.
  - Rubin, Dr. Albert L., undated; AV65 (Box 1, Reel AV65, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV65)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration 16 min.
  - Salisbury, Harrison, undated; AV66 (Box 1, Reel AV66, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV66)
    Housing Annotations: "NY Times #1, Russia"
  - Schmitt, Dr. Roland W. -- The Future of Electronics, May 31, 1968; AV67 (Box 1, Reel AV67, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV67)
  - Shary, D., undated; AV68 (Box 1, Reel AV68, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV68)
    Housing Annotations: "2 shows"
  - Skinner, B.F., undated; AV69 (Box 1, Reel AV69, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV69)
    Housing Annotations: "B.F. Skinner, Professor of Psychology Harvard U."
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 9 min.
  - Sprague, Peter, undated; AV72 (Box 2, Reel AV72, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV72)
  - Wilkins, Roy, undated; AV73 (Box 2, Reel AV73, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV73)
  - Wollin, Goesta & Ericson, David B. -- Geology, undated; AV74 (Box 2, Reel AV74, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV74)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio
  - Art Critics in Residence I, May 6, 1975; AV75 (Box 2, Reel AV75, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV75)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 97 min.
  - Art Critics in Residence II, January 21, 1975; AV76 (Box 2, Reel AV76, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV76)
    Harold Rosenberg
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 21 min.
  - Art Critics in Residence I, February 18, 1975; AV77 (Box 2, Reel AV77, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV77)
  - Art Critics in Residence I, March 11, 1975; AV78 (Box 2, Reel AV78, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV78)
  - Art Critics in Residence I, April 14, 1975; AV79 (Box 2, Reel AV79, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV79)
  - Art Critics in Residence II, April 14, 1975; AV80 (Box 2, Reel AV80, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV80)
  - Art Critics in Residence I, June 17, 1975; AV81 (Box 2, Reel AV81, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV81)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 63 min.
  - Bedford-Stuyvesant Clinics, Part 2, 1962 March 13; AV83; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 2, Reel 83)
    This recording appears to be part two of the recording "Urban League Presents: Bedford-Stuyvesant Looks to Psychiatric Needs" on AV523. It is unclear whether this recording ever aired on WNYU.
    Related Material
    This tape is related to materials in RG 39.5, Records of WNYU (Radio Station: New York, N.Y.). Also see ref140 (AV523): Urban League Presents: Bedford-Stuyvesant Looks to Psychiatric Needs in AV collection
  - Art Critics in Residence, June 17, 1975; AV82 (Box 2, Reel AV82, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV82)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 58 min.
  - Deems Lectures III [1 of 2], October 6, 1975; AV84 (Box 2, Reel AV84, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV84)
  - Deems Lectures III [2 of 2], October 6, 1975; AV85 (Box 2, Reel AV85, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV85)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 30 min.
  - Deems Lectures I, October 14, 1975; AV86 (Box 2, Reel AV86, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV86)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 85 min.
  - Deems Lectures III, part 2, October 16, 1975; AV87 (Box 2, Reel AV87, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV87)
  - Hester Inauguration, Part I Intro, October 26, 1962; AV88 (Box 2, Reel AV88, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV88)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 27 min.
  - Dinner for President Hester, May 30, 1975; AV90 (Box 2, Reel AV90, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV90)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 26 min.
  - Commencement, reel 1 of 6, June 5, 1975; AV91 (Box 2, Reel AV91, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV91)
    Reel 4 missing
  - Commencement, reel 2 of 6, June 5, 1975; AV92 (Box 2, Reel AV92, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV92)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 31 min.
  - Commencement, reel 3 of 6, June 5, 1975; AV93 (Box 2, Reel AV93, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV93)
  - Commencement, reel 5 of 6, June 5, 1975; AV94 (Box 2, Reel AV94, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV94)
  - Commencement, reel 6 of 6, June 5, 1975; AV95 (Box 2, Reel AV95, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV95)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 3 min.
  - IGA Council, undated; AV96 (Box 2, Reel AV96, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV96)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 28 min.
  - Italian Centennial, Tape I, 1961 April 17; AV97; 1 sound tape reels (Box 2, Item 97)
    Stoddard, George Dinsmore, 1897-1981; Ortona, Egidio, 1910-1996; Pollock, Thomas Clark, 1902-1988
  - Italian Centennial, Tape II, 1961 April 17; AV98; 1 sound tape reels (Box 2, Reel 98)
    Salomone, A. William (Arcangelo William), 1915-1989
  - Italian Centennial, Tape III, 1961 April 17; AV99; 1 sound tape reels (Box 2, Reel 99)
  - Lasser Conference III, May 12, 1975; AV100 (Box 2, Reel AV100, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV100)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 72 min.
  - Lasser Conference II, May 21, 1975; AV101 (Box 2, Reel AV101, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV101)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 81 min.
  - Lasser Conference III, May 27, 1975; AV102 (Box 2, Reel AV102, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV102)
  - Demertzis, Ares -- "Games", undated; AV103 (Box 2, Reel AV103, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV103)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 25 min.
  - Jerseir [unclear], WF -- "Games", undated; AV104 (Box 2, Reel AV104, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV104)
  - Openings and Closings, undated; AV105 (Box 2, Reel AV105, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV105)
  - Soaps, Part III, undated; AV106 (Box 2, Reel AV106, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV106)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 24 min.
  - Sororities, undated; AV107 (Box 2, Reel AV107, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV107)
  - University of Florida Speech Part I, undated; AV108 (Box 2, Reel AV108, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV108)
  - Speech Part 2, undated; AV109 (Box 2, Reel AV109, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV109)
  - Urban League Head Opening, undated; AV110 (Box 2, Reel AV110, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV110)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 1 min.
  - Closings for Urban League, undated; AV111 (Box 2, Reel AV111, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV111)
    Original Format: ¼" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 4 min.
  - IGA [illegible], undated; AV112 (Box 2, Reel AV112, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV112)
  - Speech by John F. Kennedy, 1960; AV113; 1 sound tape reels (Box 2, Reel 113, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 39, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV113)
    Existence and Location of Copies
    Accessible at the University Archives
    Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963
  - [Lecture on Welsh Music by Sandor Reich], undated; AV114 (Box 3, Reel AV114, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV114)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 23 min., Preservation note: "The lecture portions have audio in the left channel only, but the music samples have audio in both channels."
  - Pipes and Pedals of New York, 1962 August 6; AV115; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels 28:38; 1/4" audio tape reel (Box 3, Reel AV115)
    This tape is related to materials in RG 39.5, Records of WNYU (Radio Station: New York, N.Y.).
    This recording concerns the history of organ instruments. It was created by the Documentary Unit of the Communications Arts Group and broadcasted on WNYU. The host was Walt Michaels and the organist player featured on the recording is Dick Wolitoch.
    Physical/Technical notes
    Recorded on Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M) at 7 1/2 IPS.
    New York University. Communication Arts Group
  - Mr. Bernard Weissman, Donated Dental Building, undated; AV116 (Box 3, Reel AV116, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV116)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 3 min.
  - [A recording of popular music], 1960-1970; AV117 (Box 3, Reel AV117, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV117)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 15 min.
  - The Urban League Presents, "Rent Control and You," Part 2, undated; AV119 (Box 3, Reel AV119, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV119)
  - Law School Bicentennial [1 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV122 (Box 3, Reel AV122, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV122)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio [Master], Duration: 33 min., Speed: 7.5 IPS
  - Law School Bicentennial [2 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV123 (Box 3, Reel AV123, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV123)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio [Master], Duration: 32 min., Speed: 7.5 IPS
  - Law School Bicentennial [3 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV124 (Box 3, Reel AV124, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV124)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio [Master], Duration: 41 min., Speed: 7.5 IPS
  - Law School Bicentennial [4 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV125 (Box 3, Reel AV125, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV125)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio [Master], Duration: 52 min., Speed: 7.5 IPS
  - Law School Bicentennial [5 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV126 (Box 3, Reel AV126, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV126)
  - Law School Bicentennial [6 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV127 (Box 3, Reel AV127, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV127)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio [Master], Duration: 44 min., Speed: 7.5 IPS
  - Law School Bicentennial [7 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV128 (Box 3, Reel AV128, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV128)
  - Law School Bicentennial [8 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV129 (Box 3, Reel AV129, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV129)
  - Law School Bicentennial [9 of 9], 1976-04-27; AV130 (Box 3, Reel AV130, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV130)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio [Master], Duration: 25 min., Speed: 7.5 IPS
  - Law School Bicentennial [1 of 8], 1976-04-28; AV131 (Box 3, Reel AV131, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV131)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio [Master], Duration: 31 min., Speed: 7.5 IPS
  - Law School Bicentennial [2 of 8], 1976-04-28; AV132 (Box 3, Reel AV132, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV132)
  - Law School Bicentennial [3 of 8], 1976-04-28; AV133 (Box 3, Reel AV133, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV133)
  - Law School Bicentennial [4 of 8], 1976-04-28; AV134 (Box 3, Reel AV134, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV134)
  - Law School Bicentennial [5 of 8], 1976-04-28; AV135 (Box 3, Reel AV135, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV135)
  - Law School Bicentennial [7 of 8], 1976-04-28; AV137 (Box 3, Reel AV137, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV137)
  - Law School Bicentennial [6 of 8], 1976-04-28; AV136 (Box 3, Reel AV136, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV136)
  - Law School Bicentennial [8 of 8], 1976-04-28; AV138 (Box 3, Reel AV138, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV138)
    Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio [Master], Duration: [unknown], Speed: 7.5 IPS
  - Law School Bicentennial [1 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV139 (Box 3, Reel AV139, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV139)
  - Law School Bicentennial [2 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV140 (Box 3, Reel AV140, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV140)
  - Law School Bicentennial [3 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV141 (Box 3, Reel AV141, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV141)
  - Law School Bicentennial [4 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV142 (Box 3, Reel AV142, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV142)
  - Law School Bicentennial [5 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV143 (Box 3, Reel AV143, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV143)
  - Law School Bicentennial [9 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV147 (Box 3, Reel AV147, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV147)
  - Law School Bicentennial [6 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV144 (Box 3, Reel AV144, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV144)
  - Law School Bicentennial [7 of 10], 1976-04-29; AV145 (Box 3, Reel AV145, Box Digitized Access Files, File AV145)